A Guide to the Isle of Wight County Museum Collection of the S. B. Barham ledgers and diaries, 1876-1897
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Isle of Wight County Museum Collection of the S. B. Barham ledgers and diaries, 1876-1897
The Library of Virginia
50200 (miscellaneous reel 6218)
1 reel microfilm
S. B. Barham
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Loaned for microfilming by the Isle of Wight County Museum, Smithfield, Virginia.
Biographical Information
Sidney Baxter Barham was born 31 May 1838 in Surry County, Virginia, to Thomas Barham and Rebecca Brice Ball Barham. Barham received his medical education at the Medical College of Virginia in Richmond, Virginia, graduating in 1861. He returned to Surry County to practice medicine. Barham served on the Surry County Board of Supervisors and represented Surry and Prince George Counties in the Virginia House of Delegates in 1893-1896 and 1903-1904. He married Hannah Ann Davis (b. 1839) on 5 February 1863, and they had three children. Barham died in Surry County 20 September 1915.
Scope and Content
Ledgers and diaries, 1876-1897, of S. B. Barham (1838-1915) of Surry County, Virginia, detailing Barham's life as a physician, a farmer, and a politician in Surry County. Some ledgers are indexed account books containing accounts owed Barham for medical services. Memoranda book, 1893-1897, contains information regarding Barham's service representing Surry and Prince George Counties in the Virginia House of Delegates.
Contents List
- S. B. Barham ledgers and diaries, 1876-1897., Extent: 1 reel. (Reel 6218)
  - Diary, 1876 (Reel 6218)
  - Ledger (indexed), 1881-1882 (Reel 6218)
  - Ledger, 1888-1889 (Reel 6218)
  - Ledger (indexed), 1888-1891 (Reel 6218)
  - Diary, 1889-1890 (Reel 6218)
  - Ledger (indexed), 1889-1890 (Reel 6218)
  - Ledger (indexed), 1890 (Reel 6218)
  - Ledger, 1890-1891 (Reel 6218)
  - Diary, 1891-1892 (Reel 6218)
  - Ledger (indexed), 1891-1893 (Reel 6218)
  - Ledger (indexed), 1891-1894 (Reel 6218)
  - Ledger (indexed), 1893-1894 (Reel 6218)
  - Memoranda book, 1893-1897 (Reel 6218)